Guide to the Photographs by and relating to Allen Ginsberg MSS.PHOTO.0450
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Photographic Prints, Series 1; 26 manuscript boxes (13 linear ft.)
  - Ginsberg by Others, Subseries 1.1; 20 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box (10.25 linear ft.)
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Paris (France); Columbus, Ohio; Vancouver, Canada; London; San Francisco (Calif.); Philadelphia; Tblisi; Jim Haynes; Mary Lucas; Jack Kerouac; Jack Moore; UCLA; Elena Seibert; Willie Alexander; George Holmes; R. E. Watlington; Arnold Newman; San Francisco Unitarian Church; Charlie Cohen
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Images from a poetry reading at the 2nd Ave. Cafe or French Restaurant in New York City; Dostoevsky's house in Leningrad/Petersburg; Ezra Pound Conference in Orono, Maine
      New York City; Leningrad; San Diego; Petersburg; Orono, Maine; Tajio Moriya; Olga Rudge; Ansen, Alan.; Lucien Carr; Karl Martin; Burroughs, William S.; James W. Granerholz; James Laughlin
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Images from the Ezra Pound Conference at the University of Maine; portraits by Ann Tompkins; visit to Eugene, Oregon; performance at the WOW Hall (1983); at a Los Angeles Bookshop
      Eugene, Oregon;; Orono, Maine; Los Angeles (Calif.); Uppsala, Sweden; Toronto; WOW Hall; Wayne Tompkins; University of Maine;; Perloff, Marjorie; Steven Taylor; Peter Prince: Trevor Carolan; Ann Goddard; Patrick Warner; Ann Tompkins; Olga Rudge; Hugh Kenner; Kevin Keady
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Black and white; images of Eastern Europe; teaching a class on William Blake; US, Soviet writer's meeting
      Naropa, Colorado; Moscow; Tblisi; London; Charlottesville, Virginia; Kevin Hayes; Penny Creeley; Creeley, Robert, 1926-2005; Tandem School
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Black and white; portraits
      Tblisi; Chicago, Ill.; Alex Federas; Michael Bergman; Ray Ellis; San Diego State University; Shuntaro Tanikwa
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Black and white; images of Canada; photo of Georgian couple; Ezra Pound Conference
      Naropa, Colorado; Victoria, British Colombia; New York; Finlayson Point; Juan de Fuca; Orono, Maine; Denmark; Kevin Hayes; Hope Anderson; Redmond, Michael; Kitsilano Auditorium;; Octopus Island Books Plus; North Park Studio; Peter Prince; Olga Rudge; Richard Garrett; Andrew Wylie; Ronald F. Moffett; Abbott, Berenice.; Arthur Miller; Duchampion Burroughs; Dave Pritchard; Holly Solomon Gallery; Gary Kramer
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Portraits; large envelopes; birthday, 50th anniversary party
      Moscow
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Passport photos; Poetry readings - Eastern Europe, New Orleans, Ohio
      San Francisco (Calif.); New Orleans; Budapest; Columbus, Ohio; Ed Foster; Eugenia E. Shelley; Modern Language Association; Wes Wilson; Chris Funkhauser; Hyacinthe Hill; Marcia Veda
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      At the waterfront; people at microphones
      Amsterdam; Charlottesville, Virginia; Carl Solomon; Hobo; Gene Brooks; Hank O'Neal; Chris Funkhauser; Femer Bertalan
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Poetry readings
      Zagreb; Steven Taylor; Damil Kalogera
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Images of recording with Hobo in Budapest; Albion Bookstore in Amherst, MA with James Baldwin; at the Noho Star restaurant in New York; "Allen Ginsberg at 60" on TV; Committee on Poetry sweat lodge; Warsaw; reading in Belgrade; readings in Skopje, Yugoslavia and Clorster; Macedonia; visit to Coney Island
      Budapest; Amherst, Massachusetts; New York; Belgrade (Serbia); Warsaw; Coney Island (New York, N.Y.); Skopje Yugoslavia; Macedonia; R. Libby Hubbard; Hale, Peter; Patrick Warner; Steven Taylor; Stanislaw Ciok; Robert Frank; Richard Garrett; Albion Bookstore; Hank O'Neal; George Holmes; Orlovsky, Peter; Vicki Starbury; Committee on Poetry; Gati Gyorgy; Czeslaw Czaplinski; Christopher Funkhauser; Noho Star; L. Russell Sargent; James Baldwin; Hobo
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Images of lunch at the University Inn Motel in Maine; with William Burroughs; letter and photos from Ann Bradley, regarding visit to A Different Light Bookstore in Los Angeles; Kerouac Plaza Memorial reading and benefit in Lowell, Massachusetts
      Lowell, Massachusetts; Toronto; Orono, Maine; Los Angeles (Calif.); Edward White; Brian Foye; Kerouac Plaza Memorial; Pat Marvin; Different Light Bookstore; Morley Markson; Corso, Gregory; University Inn Motel; Ann White; Simon Albury; Burroughs, William S.; Ann Bradley
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Images of a conference in China; Budapest; Waterloo Village
      China; Budapest; Waterloo Village; Charles Abbott; Susan Rhodes; Szekelyhidi Sandor
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      PEN Banquet; New York; funeral of Trungpa Vajracharya; postcards
      New York; Hale, Peter; Trungpa Vajracharya; Bill Plumley; David Letterman; Hank O'Neal; Hammond, John; PEN
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Brooklyn College Reading; IMAGE's 10 year birthday at Aarhus Art Museum
      William Gargan; Michael McClur; Aarhus Art Museum; Brooklyn College; IMAGE
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Images of a party in Little Italy in New York City; National Mobilization for Peace and Justice in Washington, D. C.; University of Charleston, WV
      Little Italy, New York City; Washington, D.C.; West Virginia; University of Charleston
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Images of Japan; Passover in West Orange; Washington, D. C. Capitol Building mobilization; letter; Peter Orlovsky reading at Brooklyn College; letter and images from Quebec City; Alpha Beat Soup
      Japan.; West Orange; Washington, D.C.; Quebec City; Michael McClure; Marjorie Weiss Heller; Edith Ginsberg; David Heller; David Christy; Daniel Ellsberg; Carl Solomon; Brooklyn College; Alpha Beat Soup; Orlovsky, Peter; Burroughs, William S.; William Gargan; UCLA Department of Anthropology; Robert Frank; Ralph Turner
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1987; photographs, positives, (Box 11, Folder 11)
      PEN Banquet; Walt Whitman's gravesite
      Naropa, Colorado; Burroughs, William S.; Mary Hillard; Grant LeDuc; John Penley
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1987; from a photo album (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Images from Yugoslavia
      Yugoslavia
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Images of Kerouac Memorial Plaza in Lowell, Massachusetts; Boston Book festival; Village Gate, USC; Brooklyn College "Living Poetry"; camera obscura in Tel Aviv, Snapshot Poetics Workshop; Milwaukee book signing at People's Books; Naropa Institute Summer Writing Program; Whitmanmobile
      Milwaukee; Tel Aviv; Naropa, Colorado; Lowell, Massachusetts; Boston (Mass.); USC; Violent Femmes; Stephen Gredler; People's Books; Brian Ritchie; Robert Frank; Burroughs, William S.; Jeff Poniewaz; James Ragan; Naropa Institute; Brooklyn College
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Images from Tokyo; Brooklyn College Literary Series and spring readings; Tel Aviv; John Holmes' Memorial at St. Mark's Church; PEN Benefit Dinner; Peace Now Demonstration in Tel Aviv
      Tokyo; Tel Aviv; David Amram?; Mahoto Tahashima; St. Mark's Church; PEN; William Gargan; Brooklyn College
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Images from the San Francisco Jewish Community Center; Buffalo; some negatives; San Francisco "Eco-Poetry Round-up"; Tokyo; Mark Rudd's Ranchito; San Francisco book-signing at the Booksmith; in Israel
      Israel; San Francisco (Calif.); Tokyo; Buffalo; Mark Rudd; Marc Olmstead; Michael Bergman; Micha Bar-Am; Peter Marcus; Michael McClure; Ronald Colleran; Chavez, Adele; Andy Clauser; Booksmith; Brian Graham; Christopher Funkhauser; Jewish Community Center; Marc Franklin; Marc Geller
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Australia, painting; Hershey hotel, Philadelphia, PA; Association Writing Programs Convention; Naropa; Museum of American Folk Art
      William Oppenheimer
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Vancouver, British Columbia; Center Moriches; Lower Squawk Naked City Coffee House (Howard Square); Mamun; Mick Cusimano; Robert Lee;; Warren Tallman's Bellavista House
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Vancouver, Canada; New York City; Denmark; Berlin (Germany); Cambridge, MA; Warren Tallman's Bellavista House; Center Moriches; Christien Le Bars; Albert Hofmann Foundation; Ashok Sarbar; Eigner, Larry; Howard Finster; Eli Saltman; Frank Moore; Linda Mac; Foley, Jack; Italian Culture Center; Museum of American Folk Art; Corso, Gregory; Mick Cusimano; Mamun; Lower Squawk Naked City Coffee House (Howard Square); Rob Lee; RMDC Stupa Project; Rick Berman; P. Hansen; Shippensburg University; Sawang Muckapo; Saul Shapiro; Rod Kersher
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Art
      Jack Smith Memorial; Lisa Law; Myles Aronowitz; Ira Cohen; Langston Hughes Festival; Robert Bly; Tania Elezov; Bailey, Philip Hansen; Richard Bartkey; Alexy Kazshinov; Armen Kachaturian; Gaetano Kazuo Maida; Harmonia Mundi; Art Against AIDS; David Allen
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Seoul, South Korea; Paris (France); Portland; Staten Island. NY; Buffalo, NY; Kara Moore; Michael Hess; Jeff Poniewaz; Jim Cohen; Bailey, Philip Hansen; Bei Dao; QE2; Antler; Naropa Institute; Anne Waldman; Peter Cole; American Book Awards; Germain Droogenbroodt; Faustin Bray; Sonnd Photosynthesis; Eliot Greenspan; Tong-Choon Shin; Dan Wilcox; James Raga; Hanyang University; Han Yi Balk; Half Moon Cafe; SUNY
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Yugoslavia; Seoul, South Korea; Frankfurt, Germany; Paris (France); Patterson, NJ; WCW Celebration; Serge Tamagnot; Roger Barone; Melissa C. Beckman; Anne Waldman; Bei Dao; Frank Tedesco; Irena Edrovska; Jack Shuai; Jacob Burckhardt; Jung Kwang; Vonnegut, Kurt; Kangnung National University; Kung-dal Min; Leslie Fidler
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      New York City; Delhi, NY; Buffalo, NY; Portland; Istanbul, Turkey; Paris (France); Hotel des Marroniers; Joel Gaidemak; Max Wickert; Serge Tamagnot; Ursula B. Day; Centre Georges Pompidou
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Paris (France); Waterloo Village, NJ; Rochester, NY; New York City; Prague, Czech Republic; Santa Monica, CA; Rome, Italy; Albany, NY; Enzo Eric Toccaceli; Hotel des Marroniers; B. Descamps; Brooklyn Friends School; Anne Waldman; Majales Festival; Mark Carlson; Joe Gross; Laurie Mercer; Jennifer Girard; Jim Cohen; Jane Morrissey; Jaroslav Kratochvil; Michel Bulteau; Michael Schumacher; P. Panayiotis; Mustek Cafe; Psychedelic Solution Gallery; Patrice Jacovelli; Havel, Václav; Crumb, R.; QE2; Rochester Museum of Art; Robert Monsees; South Carolina ETV Network (PBS); Ryan Weederman; Tom Vitale; Tirc Wein
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Indianapolis, IN; New York City; Los Angeles (Calif.); Hannah Litzky; Doug Redding; Burroughs, William S.; CUNY; Carl Solomon; Butler University; Brian Roberts; Robert Frank; Bill Rich; Susan Neville; American Academy; Robert A. Wilson; Rich Goodhart; Philomene Long; Maria Wetzel; Leslie Howard Gallery; John Thomas; Joel & Melinda Gaidewash; JC van Itallie
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      St. Beat, France; Boulder, Colorado; New York City; Delhi, NY; Princeton, NJ; Radford, VA; Hannah Litzky; JC van Itallie; Jerry Rothenburg; Joel, Melinda & Jacob Gaidewas; Daphne Hawkes; Ed White; Gretchen Peters; Radford University; Sid Kaplan; Union Square Gallery; Brooklyn College; Corso, Gregory; William Gargan; Leslie Howard Gallery; Myles Arnowitz; Phillip Estrada; Pierre Toris
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      France; Chicago, Ill.; Lexington, VA; Detroit, Mich.; Santa Monica, CA; Bob Rosenthal; Pitzer College; Misao Mizuno; Rich Goodhart; Resisters' League; Herbert Ascherman, Jr.; Matthew P. Barbour; Ed Grazda; Holly Solomon Gallery; Claremont College; Michael Hoover; Carl Solomon; McCabe's Guitar Shop; W. Patrick Hinley; Virginia Military Institute bookstore; Washington & Lee University bookstore; Rob Lee; Rich Wilson; Thomas Felegy; Robert Haller
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Torino, Italy; Dublin, Ireland; Utopia Americana; Small Press Book Fair; Project Arts Dublin '92; Bruce Ricker; David Greenburg; Corso, Gregory; American Academy of Arts and Letters; Ira Cohen; Felicity Mason; Enzo Eric Toccaceli; Nasir Ali Mamun; M. Sato; James Laughlin Gathering; Jack Kerouac Festival
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Netherlands; Aspen, CO; San Jose (Calif.); Cape Breton, Nova Scotia, Canada; France; Poetry Conference Festival; Bruce Isacson; Poets for Life Benefit; CUNY (Brooklyn College); Nasir Ali Mamun; Paterson Museum; Anne Waldman; Keith Richards; Michael Schumacher; Victor Bockris; Di Prima, Diane; H. Silverman
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Amsterdam, Netherlands; Bottmingen, Switzerland; Eindhoven, Netherlands; Brian Graham; Vera Isler; Joy Arpots; Flip Franssen; Pach Bros. Photography; Marvin Moore
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Portraits
      San Francisco (Calif.); Miriam Berkley; Marvin Moore; Steve Lewis; Gus Van Sant; Brian Graham
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Includes written records
      Cape Breton, Nova Scotia, Canada; Eindhoven, Netherlands; Toulouse, France; P.H. Segura; Joy Arpots; Pearl Bowman; Brian Graham; Pach Bros. Photography; CUNY; Yves Le Pellec; D.H. Brown; property of Rudy Warlitzer; Flip Franssen; Gampo Abbey
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Germany; France; Graham Seidman; Limberlost Press; Pierre Chevalier; C. Funkhouserm; Flavien Gillie
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      San Francisco (Calif.); Barcelona (Spain); Poland; France; Vienna, Austria; Grand Rapids, MI; Aronson, Jerry; Jewel Heart Summer Retreat; Kurt Eisenlohr; Grand Rapids Community College; Mahmud Shurayh; Graham Seidman; Michele Curel; Duane Palyka; Piotr Sumara; David Cope; Roxie Theater
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Hailey, ID; Edwardsville, IL; Oslo, Norway; Munich, Germany; Czechoslovakia; Rosemary Ardinger; Rick Ardinger; Lawrence Schwarzwald; Ivo Dokovpil; Drumvoices Revue; Angelika Krinzinger; Stein Beyer-Olsen; Southern Illinois University at Edwardsville; Schule fuer Dichtung in Wien
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      London, England; San Francisco (Calif.); Galway, Ireland; Lodz, Poland; Belgrade (Serbia); Whalen, Philip; Maria Wasko; Michael McClure; Gus Van Sant; Howard Hart; Ian Hilroy; Cafe Trieste; Astor Place Bookshop; Brain Graham; Orlovsky, Peter; Huncke, Herbert; Andy Clausen; Vesna Pavlovic; Corso, Gregory; Shig Murao
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Galway, Ireland; Dublin, Ireland; Seattle, WA; Berlin (Germany); Columbia University; Cathal Dawson; Joe Pineiro; Ilene Markay-Hallack; Michael Andeel; Joel Sartori; Bernard Mindich; Lothar Deus
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Boulder, Colorado; Washington, D.C.; Arapahoe Pass, CO; Boulder Public Library; David Cope; David Dellinger; Steve Miles; Amiri Baraka; Naropa Institute; Anne Waldman; Antler; Yves Le Pellec; Boulder High School; Kerouac School; Snyder, Gary; Jim Cohn; Miriam Sanders; Allen Clausen; Malcolm Steiner; Allen Ginsberg Library; Galway Kinnell; Felinghetti; Sanders, Ed; Jeff Poniewaz
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      Belgrade (Serbia); Asheville, NC; France; Oakland (Calif.); New York City; Hot Springs, AR; Ball, Gordon; Allen Ginsberg Library; Snyder, Gary; Attila Gyenis; Boulder Public Library; Columbia-Greene Community College; Dusan Gojkov; Thomas Wolfe Memorial; Eliot Greenspan; Zoran Calle; Gary Goldberg; Justine Herbert; Hale, Peter; Naropa Institute; Scott Goodrich; St. Mark's Church; New York City Town Hall; Ted Mitchell; New York University
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      New York City; Lowell, MA; La Jolla, CA; Brooklyn, NY; Tatsuo Aburamoto; Terry Williams; Doug Knutson; Tino Villanueva; D.G. Willis Books; Library of Christopher Columbus; Frank Csongos; Philip Glass; New York University
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Includes model release document and photographic "Tribute to Allen Ginsberg"
      St. Denis; Paris (France); Washington, D.C.; New York City; Princeton Junction; Seth Brigham; Felver, Christopher; Geoffrey Pankhurst; Paul Roth; David Savage; Jewel Heart; Bruce Giffin; Aronson, Jerry; Metro Timer Retreat; Maxime Godard; Pacific Graduate Institute; Naomi Savage
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Includes Ginsberg form response letter to fan mail; letters; signing Holy Soul Jelly
      Paris (France); San Francisco (Calif.); New Jersey; Berkeley (Calif.) -- History.; Naropa, Colorado; Los Angeles (Calif.); Aronson, Jerry; James Arkatov; Merry Pranksters; Althea Crawford; Napoleon I, Emperor of the French; Abraham Aronow; Kronos Quartet; Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009; Ted Mitchell; Boulder Theater; Thomas Wolfe Memorial; McMahon, Angus; Naropa Arapaho Lodge; Andy Clausen; Sophie Bassouls; American Academy of Arts and Letters; George Walker; East Restaurant; Virginia Dajani; Dorothy Alexander; Corso, Gregory; W. T. Pfefferle; David Sellers; Kesey, Ken
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Images of Fiedler Fest at State University of New York
      Cleveland; Cheltenham; Paris (France); New York City; Galway; Sotheby & Co. (London, England); Sam Abrams; Richard Oldenburg; Philip Glass; Clemente, Francesco; State University of New York; St. Mark's Poetry Project; Voznesenskīĭ, Andreĭ; Andy Clausen; Charles Henri Ford; Angie Roberts; Allen DeLoch; Gelek Rinpoche; James Dowell; Colleen Fullbright; Don Bapst; Eliot Katz; Fery Toosi; Martha Cooper; Oberlin College; Ofer Levy; Hale, Peter; Corso, Gregory; Jewel Heart; John Kolomvakis; Leanne Brown; Lollapalooza
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      New York City; Chenonceau; Los Angeles (Calif.); Turin; New York University Press; Bruno Bischofberger; Naropa Institute; Bowles, Paul, 1910–1999; Peter Semple; Clemente, Francesco; Gyula Gazdag;; Georgian Court College; Lisa Hammond; Karl Schondorfer; Corman, Cid; Diego Cortez; Felver, Christopher; Dave Bailey; Turin Film Festival; Sogo Ishii; Christina Bischofberger; Cabana Carioca; Virginia Carr; Carl Rahosi
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Includes letters
      Witten, Germany; Italy; William Gargan; American Academy of Arts and Letters; St. Mark's Church Poetry Project; Symbiosis Films; John Kolomvakis; Marc Peloquin; James Dowell; Jo Ann Wasserman; Gino Mario De Faveri; Ed Friedman; Dorothy Alexander; Carsten Hohenhoff; Brooklyn College; Bob Dylan; Betsey Feeley; Andrea Zanzotto
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Includes correspondence
      Germany; Boulder, Colorado; Chinatown, New York City; Cleveland; Camden; Wayne Lee Radziminski; Amiri Baraka; Greenfield-Sanders, Timothy; Andrea Zanzotto; Thomas Reed; Arthur Miller; Thomas Karsten; Arthur Schlesinger; The Cooler; Asako; Benjamin Dimmitt; Shana Dressler; Chris Felber; Quentin Crisp; Kino Traumstern Film Theater; Karl Schondorfer; Marcellino Giubilato; Marc Peloquin; Hale, Peter; Myles Aronowitz; Philip Glass; Peter Semple; Dorothy Alexander; Danny Meacher; Jennifer Girard; Malanga, Gerard; Jeronym Janicek; Jenny Miller; Kai Sibley; Jewel Heart
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      New York; Moscow, Russia; Milwaukee; Ann Arbor; Rochester, New York; William Gargan; Robert Frank; Rochester Zen Center; San Francisco Public Library, North Beach Branch; Smithsonian National Portrait Gallery; Steve Shelley; Steven Taylor; Tara Limbaugh; Whitney Museum; David Sachter; Brooklyn College; Ed deGrazia; Ferlinghetti, Lawrence; De Young Museum; Barnes and Noble; Anton Corbijn; Brian Foye; Barney Rossett; Papazian, Albert; American Cemetery; Alexander Cheparukhin; John Grady; John Weiners; Jewel Heart Benefit; Joan Vollmer Burroughs; Kazuo Ohno; Larry Keenan; Jonathan Rose; Jorge Ferez; Gary Rasmussen; Green Wave International; Gangchen Rinpoche Center; Gardner Haskell; Ian Ayres; Ira Cohen; Norman Fischer; New York University; Nancy Peters; Milwaukee Gay Pridefest; Rachel Rose; Philip Glass; Paterson Poetry Marathon; Lisa Phillips; Corso, Gregory; Lenny Kaye; Lee Reynaldo; Huncke, Herbert; Mike Griffin; McCabe's; Orlovsky, Peter; Mark Ewert; Marc Albert-Levin
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      Naples, Italy; De Young Museum; Vittorio Guida; Dennis Hopper; Larry Keenan; Spencer Higgins; Orlovsky, Peter; Tibet House; Brook Dillon; Ball, Gordon; St. Martin's; Charles Carroll
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Los Angeles (Calif.); Ira Cohen; Ed Grazda; Denise Keim; Carolyn K. Carr; St. Mark's Church; Whitney Museum; Robert Frank; Robert Koch; Sergey Bermeniev; Smithsonian Institution; National Portrait Gallery; Richard B. Nagler; Robert Berman Gallery; Robert Berman
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1996; one photo needs cover! (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Includes article on Dan Nicoletta's photos of gay culture
      Tangier, Morocco; Newark, New Jersey; Washington, D.C.; Michael McClure; Amiri Baraka; National Portrait Gallery;; Mark Ewert; Mercury Records; Lenny Kaye; Brice, Lindsay; Lee Ranaldo; Kenward Elmslie; Jello Biafra; Kim Deale; Orlovsky, Peter; Ken Taranto; Eric Drooker; Essex County College; Kenneth Koch; John Gribbin; Diane Arbus; Jonathan Williams; Ed Gilbert; Jillian Clark; Bob Kelley; Joan Rothfuss; Daniel Nicoletta; Bowles, Paul, 1910–1999; Corso, Gregory; Ferlinghetti, Lawrence; Burroughs, William S.; Walker Arts Center; Tom McIntyre; St. Mark's Church; Smithsonian Institute; Creeley, Robert, 1926-2005; Scott Pimintel; Richard Nagler; Ansen, Alan.; Paule Anglim
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1996; slides, photos (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Includes letter from James Hopkins with a bodi leaf from Bodh Gaya, India
      Poland; Bodh Gaya, India;; Grand Hotel; Gemini GEL; Elsa Dorfman; Robert Berman; David Robertson; UC Davis; Brigitte Cornand; Larry Keenan; Bob Rosenthal; Brice, Lindsay; James Hopkins; John Gribbin
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Orlovsky, Peter; Hobo; Lynn Davis
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1997; photos, slides (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Photographs of Allen Ginsberg's Loft in New York, done by Sid Kaplan
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      Includes advertisement for talks by Buddhist leader Jamgon Kongtrul Rinpoche; advertisment for a Buddhist calendar, and letterhead; Shambhala Edict on Wholesome Human Conduct; postcard; Buddhist art; red folder
      Paris (France); New York; Albuquerque (N.M.); Boulder; Blair Hansen; Brian Graham; Richard Nagler; Chuck Pintle; Naropa Institute; Dharmadatu of New York;; Marvin Moore; Karma Thegsum Choling, Tibetan Buddhist Meditation Center; Jennifer Girard; Jamgon Kongtrul Rinpoche; Apollinaire's grave; Guillaume Apollinaire
    - Allen Ginsberg, 1955-59 (Item 16.1, Folder 1)
      Toronto
    - Ginsberg by others, 1976 (Item 16.1, Folder 2)
    - Ginsberg by others, 1986 (Item 16.1, Folder 3)
    - Ginsberg by others, 1992 (Item 16.1, Folder 4)
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1926-1959 (Item 17, Folder 1)
    - Ginsberg by Others, 1960 (Item 17, Folder 2)
      Portrait at 170 E 2nd St in New York City